Anton Ryzhenko

Front End developer

anton.ryzhenko@tuta.io





Geradot



+1 (712) 449-6101

Summary



A junior front-end developer with a little experience in full-stack development and more in content management. My pet projects are on my Github account.



Certificates



«CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript» from 2023 HarvardX: bit.ly/3IKJAzv

«Front-end. Complete course for beginners from Ciklum»: 2023 bit.ly/3LTiXD6

Work experience



Future Search

09/2022 - 03/2023

Content Manager

- I managed to implement a plugin that allows you to work with the design of TablePress WordPress tables at the CSS code level.
- Implemented convenient reporting Google Sheets for various purposes (fixing bugs on sites, copywriter errors, etc.).



06/2016 - 12/2016

Full Stack Developer

Expanded functionality for generating text documents using the PHPWord library.

Education



Bogdan Khmelnitsky Melitopol state pedagogical 2012 - 2016 university

Faculty of Mathematics, Informatics and Economics Specialty: Computer Science (bachelor)

Professional Skills

SPA development	• • • • •
Semantic layout	• • • • •
Adaptive design	

Technical skills

HTML	• • • • •
CSS/Sass	••••
JavaScript	• • • • 0
Bootstrap	• • • • •
Next.JS	• • • • •
React.JS	• • • • •
Python/Django	• • • • • •

Languages

Ukrainian	••••
Russian	••••
English	• • • • •